[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1102_0201_abandonedduties",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 46,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1102_0201_d_00_Container_abandonedduties",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1102_Magistrate",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1102_0201_abandonedduties_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1102_0201_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1102_0201_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1102_0201_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1102_0201_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1102_0201_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1102_0201_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1105_0201_teardropgems",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 47,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1105_0201_d_00_Container_teardropgems",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1105_Artificer",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1105_0201_teardropgems_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1105_0201_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1105_0201_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1105_0201_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1105_0201_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1105_0201_e_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1105_0201_f_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1105_0202_excommunication",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1105_0202_d_00_Container_excommunication",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1105_Artificer",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_04",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1105_0202_excommunication_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1105_0202_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1105_0202_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1105_0202_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1105_0202_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1105_0202_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1105_0202_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1104_0201_waterfalls",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1104_0201_d_00_Container_waterfalls",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1104_Overseer",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1104_0201_waterfalls_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1104_0201_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1104_0201_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1104_0201_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1104_0201_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1104_0201_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1104_0201_f_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1111_0201_deluge",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1111_0201_d_00_Container_deluge",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1111_Stranger",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1111_0201_deluge_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1111_0201_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1111_0201_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1111_0201_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1111_0201_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1111_0201_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1111_0201_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1111_0301_roadtotruth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1111_0301_d_00_Container_roadtotruth",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1111_Stranger",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_02",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1111_0301_roadtotruth_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1111_0301_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1111_0301_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1111_0301_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1111_0301_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1111_0301_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1111_0301_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1111_0401_ancienttruth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1111_0401_d_00_Container_ancienttruth",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1111_Stranger",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1111_0401_ancienttruth_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1111_0401_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1111_0401_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1111_0401_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1111_0401_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1111_0401_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1111_0401_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1102_0301_musslebeard",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1102_0301_d_00_Container_musslebeard",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1102_Magistrate",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1102_0301_musslebeard_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1102_0301_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1102_0301_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1102_0301_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1102_0301_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1102_0301_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1102_0301_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1111_0402_corruptedenergy",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1111_0402_d_00_Container_corruptedenergy",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1111_Stranger",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_08",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1111_0402_corruptedenergy_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1111_0402_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1111_0402_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1111_0402_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1111_0402_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1111_0402_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1111_0402_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1102_0401_march",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1102_0401_d_00_Container_march",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1102_Magistrate",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Quest_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1102_0401_march_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1102_0401_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1102_0401_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1102_0401_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1102_0401_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1102_0401_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1102_0401_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "MourningdaleArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1104_01a01_crashing",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 45,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1104_01a01_d_00_Container_crashing",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1103_Survivalist",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Quest_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1104_01a01_crashing_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1104_01a01_a_Title",
		"Description": "@1104_01a01_b_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1104_01a01_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1104_01a01_c_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1104_01a01_e_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1104_01a01_f_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1124_0101_EnPleinAire",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 45,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1124_0101_Container_OdeToAeternum",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1124_PierreAuguste",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Pierre_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Title",
		"Description": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1124_0101_EnPleinAire_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 45,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1126_0101_Container_StoneColdSecrets",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1126_Leilani",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Leilani_1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Pierre_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Title",
		"Description": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1126_0101_StoneColdSecrets_Complete_Available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1126_0102_TheLastMystery",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 47,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1126_0102_Container_TheLastMystery",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1126_Leilani",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Leilani_2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Leilani_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Title",
		"Description": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1126_0102_TheLastMystery_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1126_0102_Atoast",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 47,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1126_0102_Container_Atoast",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1110_Barkeep",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Leilani_3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Leilani_2",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1126_0102_Atoast_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1126_0102_Atoast_Title",
		"Description": "@1126_0102_Atoast_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1126_0102_Atoast_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1126_0102_Atoast_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1126_0102_Atoast_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1126_0102_Atoast_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 47,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1126_0103_Container_AmateurAdventurer",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1124_PierreAuguste2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Pierre_2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Leilani_3",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Title",
		"Description": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1126_0103_AmateurAdventurer_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1125_0101_SongoftheSea",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 46,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1125_0101_Container_SongoftheSea",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1125_McKeys",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_McKeys_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Title",
		"Description": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1125_0101_SongoftheSea_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1128_0101_VillageChampion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1128_0101_Container_VillageChampion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1128_Lerato",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Lerato_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1128_0101_VillageChampion_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_Title",
		"Description": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1128_0101_VillageChampion_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1127_0101_MalignDominion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1127_0101_container_MalignDominion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1127_Harunobu",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Harunobu_1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Lerato_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1127_0101_MalignDominion_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_Title",
		"Description": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1127_0101_MalignDominion_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1127_0102_MakinBacon",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1127_0102_Container_MakinBacon",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1127_Harunobu",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Harunobu_2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Harunobu_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1127_0102_MakinBacon_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_Title",
		"Description": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1127_0102_MakinBacon_Complete_Available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1129_0101_SoulMusic",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1129_0101_Container_SoulMusic",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1129_Jaansen",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Jaansen_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1127_0102_SoulMusic_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_Title",
		"Description": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1129_0101_SoulMusic_Complete_Available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1129_0102_JaansenintheNorth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1129_0102_Container_JaansenintheNorth",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1129_Jaansen2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Jaansen_x",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Jaansen_1",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1129_0102_jaanseninthenorth_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_Title",
		"Description": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1129_0102_Janinthenorth_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1129_0102_NewPerspective",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1129_0102_Container_NewPerspective",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1129_Jaansen2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Jaansen_2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Jaansen_x",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1127_0102_NewPerspective_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_Title",
		"Description": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1129_0102_NewPerspective_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1129_0103_CliffHanger",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 48,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1129_0103_Container_CliffHanger",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1129_Sculpture",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Jaansen_3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Jaansen_2",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1127_0102_CliffHanger_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_Title",
		"Description": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1129_0103_CliffHanger_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 50,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1110_0101_container_GreetTheNewcomers",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1127_Harunobu2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Barkeep_1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Harunobu_2",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Title",
		"Description": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 50,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1127_0101_Container_GreetTheNewcomers2",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1128_Lerato2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Harunobu2_1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Harunobu_2",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Title",
		"Description": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1110_0101_GreetTheNewcomers2_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1124_PierreGoHome",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 50,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1124_Container_PierreGoHome",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1124_PierreAuguste",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_Pierre_3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "11_Pierre_2",
		"RequiredLevel": 40,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1124_PierreGoHome_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1124_PierreGoHome_Title",
		"Description": "@1124_PierreGoHome_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1124_PierreGoHome_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1124_PierreGoHome_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1124_PierreGoHome_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1124_PierreGoHome_Complete_Available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1140_Halloween_02",
		"Type": "Event",
		"DifficultyLevel": 35,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1140_Halloween_02_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1140_Halloween_Salvatore",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "11_HalloweenQuest2",
		"RequiredLevel": 35,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1140_Halloween_02_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1140_Halloween_02_TitleB",
		"Description": "@1140_Halloween_02_DescriptionB",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1140_Halloween_02_start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1140_Halloween_02_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1140_Halloween_02_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1140_Halloween_02_Available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "EventHalloween"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1101_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1101_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1102_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1102_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1103_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1103_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1104_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1104_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1105_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1105_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1106_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1106_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1107_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1107_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1108_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1108_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1109_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1109_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1110_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1110_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1101_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1101_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1102_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1102_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1103_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1103_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1104_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1104_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1105_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1105_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1106_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1106_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1107_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1107_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1108_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1108_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1109_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1109_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1110_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1110_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1101_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1101_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1102_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1102_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1103_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1103_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1104_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1104_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1105_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1105_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1106_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1106_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1107_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1107_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1108_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1108_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1109_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1109_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1110_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1110_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1161_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1161_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1162_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1162_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1163_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1163_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1164_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1164_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1165_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1165_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1166_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1166_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1167_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1167_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1168_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1168_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1169_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1169_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1170_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1170_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1161_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1161_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1162_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1162_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1163_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1163_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1164_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1164_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1165_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1165_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1166_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1166_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1167_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1167_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1168_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1168_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1169_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1169_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1170_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_1170_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1161_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1161_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1162_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1162_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1163_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1163_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1164_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1164_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1165_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1165_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1166_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1166_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1167_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1167_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1168_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1168_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1169_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1169_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1170_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_1170_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_11_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_H_01_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_11_H_01_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_H_02_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_11_H_02_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_11_H_03_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_11_H_03_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 11,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	}
]